completion_text: |-
  <p>lorem ipsum</p>
description: |-
  lorem ipsum
groups:
- id: intro
  pages:
  - content: "<p>lorem ipsum</p> "
    id: welcome
    title: quiz 2
    type: Page
- id: quiz_start
  pages:
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a l
    id: quizquestion42
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 1
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a la pregunta 2
    id: quizquestion43
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 2
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a la pregunta 3
    id: quizquestion44
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 3
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a la pregunta 4
    id: quizquestion45
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 4
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a la pregunta 5
    id: quizquestion46
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 5
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta  a la pregunta 6
    id: quizquestion47
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 6
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a la pregunta 7
    id: quizquestion49
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta  7
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a la pregunta 8
    id: quizquestion50
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 8
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 0.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>Respuesta a la pregunta 9
    id: quizquestion48
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta  9
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  - answers:
    - <plain>lorem ipsum
    id: quizquestion51
    prompt: ''
    title: Pregunta 10
    type: TextQuestion
    value: 1.0
  shuffle: true
rules:
  access:
  - permissions:
    - view
    - submit_answer
    - end_session
    - see_correctness
    - see_answer_after_submission
  grade_aggregation_strategy: use_latest
  grade_identifier: quiz23
  grading:
  - credit_percent: 100
  start:
  - if_before: 2020-10-31 16:22:04+00:00
    if_has_fewer_sessions_than: 1
    if_has_role:
    - student
    - ta
    - instructor
    may_list_existing_sessions: true
    may_start_new_session: true
  - may_list_existing_sessions: true
    may_start_new_session: false
title: quiz 2
